### Contact

courtneyrpowell@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ courtneyrpowellmsn (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

**ACLS** 

**BLS** 

Critical Care

### Certifications

AIDS Certified Registered Nurse (ACRN)

Certified Pediatric Emergency Nurse (CPEN)

Trauma Certified Registered Nurse (TCRN)

Certified Emergency Nurse (CEN)
Cardiac Vascular Nursing (RN-BC)

# Courtney Powell, MSN, RN, ACRN, RN-BC, CEN, TCRN, CPEN

ER Assistant Nurse Manager at Kaiser Permanente Los Angeles, California

# Summary

Experienced Emergency Room Nurse and Nurse Leader with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Board certified in several nursing specialties, including HIV/AIDS, Cardiac-Vascular, Adult & Pediatric Emergency and Trauma. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master of Science in Nursing (MSN) focused in Community Systems Administration. Currently pursuing a Master of Business Administration (MBA) from Southeastern Oklahoma State University.

# Experience

Kaiser Permanente
1 year 1 month
ER Assistant Nurse Manager
April 2020 - Present (4 months)

Nursing Supervisor
July 2019 - April 2020 (10 months)

UCSF Medical Center Emergency Room RN June 2016 - Present (4 years 2 months)

San Francisco AIDS Foundation 3 years 6 months

Registered Nurse January 2019 - May 2020 (1 year 5 months) United States

Volunteer HIV/STI Counselor

### December 2016 - January 2019 (2 years 2 months)

San Francisco Bay Area

Kaiser Permanente Emergency Room RN May 2017 - April 2019 (2 years) Oakland, California

American Mobile Healthcare
Travel Nurse
May 2015 - July 2016 (1 year 3 months)

Thomas Jefferson University Hospitals Pool RN January 2014 - May 2016 (2 years 5 months)

Princeton Healthcare System ER Assistant Nurse Manager November 2014 - May 2015 (7 months)

Pennsylvania Hospital Emergency Room Registered Nurse September 2013 - January 2014 (5 months)

Thomas Jefferson University Hospital 6 years 9 months

Emergency Room Registered Nurse September 2011 - October 2013 (2 years 2 months) greater philadelphia area

Heart Failure Registered Nurse February 2007 - September 2011 (4 years 8 months)

Keystone Home Health & Hospice HIV/AIDS Registered Nurse August 2008 - October 2009 (1 year 3 months)

Mazzoni Center
2 years 7 months
HIV/AIDS Case Manager
January 2006 - February 2007 (1 year 2 months)
Page 2 of 3

HIV Prevention Counselor August 2004 - January 2006 (1 year 6 months)

Cendant Mortgage
Pricing Analyst
July 2002 - August 2004 (2 years 2 months)

**IBM** 

Financial Analyst June 2001 - June 2002 (1 year 1 month)

# Education

Thomas Jefferson University

Master of Science Nursing (MSN), Community Systems

Administration · (2010 - 2014)

Southeastern Oklahoma State University

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Healthcare Information

Systems · (2019 - 2021)

La Salle University

Bachelor of Science Nursing (BSN), Nursing (2003 - 2006)

Jackson State University

Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA), Finance · (1996 - 2001)